<idea-plugin>
    <id>de.jaimerojas.clickup</id>
    <name>ClickUp Integration</name>
    <vendor email="jaimitorojas@gmail.com">Jaime Rojas</vendor>

    <description><![CDATA[
    <h2>ClickUp Integration for IntelliJ Platform</h2>
    <p>
    Enhance your productivity by integrating ClickUp with JetBrains IDEs. Manage your tasks seamlessly and track
    time spent on each task within your development environment.
    <h3>Features</h3>
    <ul>
        <li>Fetches issues from ClickUp spaces to use as tasks.</li>
        <li>Updates your tasks status from the IDE.</li>
        <li>Time Tracking for Ultimate users with access to the time tracking bundle.</li>
    </ul>

    <p>
    For now the plugin has limited functionality, but it is a work in progress. This plugin is an open source
    project, and is not officially supported by ClickUp, so contributions and feedback are equally welcome.
    </p>

    <p>The logo is a registered trademark of ClickUp. </p>

    <h3>Setup Instructions</h3>
    <h4>Installation</h4>
    <ol>
        <li>Open your JetBrains IDE (IntelliJ IDEA, PyCharm, WebStorm, etc.).</li>
        <li>Navigate to <code>File</code> > <code>Settings</code> (or <code>Preferences</code> on macOS).</li>
        <li>In the left-hand pane, select <code>Plugins</code>.</li>
        <li>Click on the <code>Marketplace</code> tab.</li>
        <li>In the search bar, type <code>ClickUp Integration</code>.</li>
        <li>Locate the <code>ClickUp Integration</code> plugin and click <code>Install</code>.</li>
        <li>Restart your IDE to activate the plugin.</li>
    </ol>

    <h4>Configuration</h4>
    <ol>
        <li>After restarting the IDE, go to <code>File</code> > <code>Settings</code> (or <code>Preferences</code> on macOS).</li>
        <li>In the left-hand pane, select <code>Tools</code> > <code>Tasks</code>.</li>
        <li>Click on the <code>Servers</code> tab.</li>
        <li>Click the <code>+</code> button to add a new task server.</li>
        <li>Select <code>ClickUp</code> from the list of available servers.</li>
        <li>Enter your ClickUp API token and other required information.</li>
        <li>Click <code>Test</code> to ensure the connection is successful.</li>
        <li>Click <code>OK</code> to save the configuration.</li>
    </ol>

    <h4>Using the Plugin</h4>
    <ol>
        <li>Open the <code>Tasks</code> tool window from the bottom of the IDE.</li>
        <li>You can now create, view, and manage your ClickUp tasks directly from the IDE.</li>
        <li>Use the <code>Time Tracking</code> feature to log time spent on tasks (available in IntelliJ IDEA Ultimate).</li>
    </ol>

    <h3>Troubleshooting</h3>
    <h4>Common Issues</h4>

    <ol>
        <li>Plugin Not Showing Up After Installation
            <ul>
                <li>Ensure that you have restarted your IDE after installing the plugin. </li>
                <li>Verify that the plugin is enabled in the plugin settings.</li>
            </ul>
        </li>
        <li>Unable to Connect to ClickUp
            <ul>
                <li>Double-check your ClickUp API token and ensure it is correctly entered.</li>
                <li>Test the connection in File > Settings (or Preferences on macOS) > Tools > Tasks > Servers.</li>
            </ul>
        </li>
        <li>Tasks Not Syncing
            <ul>
                <li>Ensure that your internet connection is stable.</li>
                <li>Verify that the ClickUp server is not experiencing downtime.</li>
            </ul>
        <li>Time Tracking Not Working
            <ul>
                <li>Time tracking is only available in IntelliJ IDEA Ultimate. Ensure you are using the correct version of the IDE.</li>
                <li>Check if the Time Tracking bundle is installed and enabled.</li>
            </ul>
        </li>
    </ol>

    <h4>Getting Help</h4>
    <p>
        If you encounter any issues not listed above, please create an issue on the <a href="https://github.com/jaim3r0jas/clickup-intellij-plugin/issues">GitHub Issues</a>
        page. Provide detailed information about the problem, including steps to reproduce, expected behavior, and any error messages.
    </p>
]]></description>

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>
    <depends>com.intellij.tasks</depends>
    <actions>
        <!-- Add your actions here -->
    </actions>
    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <tasks.repositoryType implementation="de.jaimerojas.clickup.ClickUpRepositoryType"/>
    </extensions>

    <change-notes><![CDATA[
    <ul>
      <li>Improve plugin documentation.</li>
    </ul>
    ]]></change-notes>
</idea-plugin>